<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <!--    Locations -->
    <!--    lalibela-->
    <string name="lalibela_name">Lalibela</string>
    <string name="lalibela_address">Ethiopia Amhara Region, North Wollo Zone</string>
    <string name="lalibela_description">Lalibela is a town in the Amhara region of northern Ethiopia.
        It\'s known for its distinctive rock-cut churches dating from the 12th and 13th centuries, which
        are pilgrimage sites for Coptic Christians. Carved out of rock, the subterranean monoliths include
        huge Bete Medhane Alem, and cross-shaped Bete Giyorgis. Many are joined by tunnels and trenches,
        and some have carved bas-reliefs and colored frescoes inside.</string>
    <!--axum -->
    <string name="axum_name">Axum</string>
    <string name="axum_address">Ethiopia Tigray Region</string>
    <string name="axum_description">Aksum is a city in northern Ethiopia. It\'s known for its tall,
        carved obelisks, relics of the ancient Kingdom of Aksum. Most are in the northern Stelae Park,
        including a huge fallen pillar, now in pieces. Centuries-old St. Mary of Zion is a Christian
        church and pilgrimage site believed to have housed the biblical Ark of the Covenant.
        The neighboring Chapel of the Tablet is said to contain the Ark today.</string>
    <!--abay -->
    <string name="abay_name">Nile River</string>
    <string name="abay_address">Ethiopia</string>
    <string name="abay_description">The Blue Nile is so called because floods during the summer monsoon
        erode a vast amount of fertile soil from the Ethiopian Highlands and carry it downstream as silt,
        turning the water dark brown or almost black.</string>
    <!--gondar -->
    <string name="gondar_name">Gondar</string>
    <string name="gondadr_address">Ethiopia</string>
    <string name="gondar_description">Gondar, or Gonder, is a city in northern Ethiopia.
        It\'s known for the walled Fasil Ghebbi fortress and palace compound, once the seat of
        Ethiopian emperors. Dominating it is the immense 17th-century castle of Emperor Fasilides,
        which combines Portuguese, Indian and local architectural styles. Outside the complex is
        Debre Berhan Selassie church, with an interior of elaborate murals, including a ceiling of faces.</string>
    <!--tiya -->
    <string name="tiya_name">Tiya</string>
    <string name="tiya_address">Ethiopia</string>
    <string name="tiya_description">Tiya is a town in central Ethiopia. It is situated in the
        Gurage Zone of the Southern Nations, Nationalities, and Peoples Region south of Addis Ababa.
        It is also the location of an archaeological site.</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>

    <!--    hotel-->
    <!--    sheraton-->
    <string name="sheraton_name">Sheraton Addis</string>
    <string name="sheraton_address"> Taitu St, Addis Ababa 1000</string>
    <string name="sheraton_description">Sheraton Addis, a Luxury Collection Hotel offers accommodations
        in Addis Ababa. Guests can enjoy the outdoor pool or relax at the spa and wellness center.</string>
    <!--    skylight-->
    <string name="skylight_name">Sky Light Addis</string>
    <string name="skylight_address">Airport Rd, Addis Ababa 1755</string>
    <string name="skylight_description">Located in Addis Ababa, Ethiopian Skylight Hotel is 0.3 miles
        from Bole International Airport and offers various facilities, such as a fitness center, swimming pool</string>
    <!--radisson-->
    <string name="radisson_name">Radisson blu</string>
    <string name="radisson_address">Kazanchis Business District Kirkos Subcity 17/18 </string>
    <string name="radisson_description">Book your Hotel in Addis Ababa online. No reservation costs.
        Great rates. Great Availability. Special Offers. No Booking Fees. Low Rates. Highlights:
        Founded In 1996, No Reservation Fees, Instant Confirmation Available.</string>

<!--food-->
<!--shiro-->
    <string name="shiro_name">Shiro</string>
    <string name="shiro_address">"Ethiopian Best food" </string>
    <string name="shiro_description">Shiro is a stew whose primary ingredient is powdered chickpeas
        or broad bean meal. It is often prepared with the addition of minced onions, garlic and,
        depending upon regional variation, ground ginger or chopped tomatoes and chili-peppers.
        Shiro is served atop injera or kitcha.</string>


    <string name="injera_name">Injera</string>
    <string name="injera_address">"Ethiopian Best food" </string>
    <string name="injera_description">Injera, ənǧära እንጀራ, is a sour fermented flatbread with a
        slightly spongy texture, traditionally made out of teff flour. It is the national dish of
        Ethiopia and Eritrea. It is central to the dining process in those cultures as bread is the
        most fundamental component.</string>
<!--    kitfo-->
    <string name="kitfo_name">Kitfo</string>
    <string name="kitfo_address">"Ethiopian Best food" </string>
    <string name="kitfo_description">Kitfo consists of minced raw beef, marinated in mitmita (a chili powder-based spice blend) and niter
        kibbeh (a clarified butter infused with herbs and spices). The word comes from the
        Ethio-Semitic root k-t-f, meaning "to chop finely; mince.</string>
</resources>
